all right
tapping dad
what all right we got we got eight
viewers we got eight viewers all right
you want to introduce yourself hi I'm
Alex she's a longtime periscope watcher
cameras time periscope participant yeah
a lot of pressure a lot of Prayer it's
like those you know when the porn stars
fucked the fans it's very similar I am
so we're driving around in comas newest
car , did legitimately buy this car get
who's eight anyone guess to who lets you
think no that's you thing guess what
race what kind of car do you guys know
we know caught no commenters there's 53
people it's rear-wheel drive drifting
doesn't really ever all wake to
definitely gonna cruise around what you
ought to be doing that no we're actually
we're going to McDonalds guys it's a
Mercedes no it's not a Mercedes not a
Mercedes nope
it is a Volvo it is a Volvo look at them
look at the steering wheel Oh their logo
hasn't changed at all same yeah alright
anyone guess what year it is yeah that's
key really this is a classic it feels
vaguely like a boat
alright it's a 1997 Volvo head guess is
99 8900 disco peas they're participating
love them let's go be spiders baby so
guys old car channel this car so much
interest um yeah so we need if anybody
has a mechanical steering system we were
looking to buy one mechanical pedal
pressing systems old cars channel this
is the new Volvo there's a channel and
slack oh yeah I was telling him how
dangerous building torque interceptors
this alright but it's secretly just
because I want them to build something
that'll work with my Volvo is a great
car tape deck I love this car I got a
great deal on this car I'm Scopus
it can be yours for $1,500 it's on
craig's
right now go on San Francisco San
Francisco Craigslist do we know Mario
who's Mario Mario yeah it's crazy Mario
this car is crazy it's crazy Mario look
at this beautiful burlwood detail yeah
we should go to the McDonald's
drive-through we're here at the good
McDonald's ok I'll go to this one
this one is big flurries I love my
weight we're only fielding legitimate
honestly no is he serious many of those
oh that's it we need to raise it to 2 K
vanilla gorilla to 2 K get 2 K 2 K ok
oh oh oh vanilla gorilla said we'd Oh
someone was offering 2 K my yeah bro
where do you wanna go she ate well we'll
start at $10 will start Julius will you
like do something nice for the person
who buys the car um they'll deliver -
right now I'll pick you up what do you
want
Donald's even off the premium menu if
you want like a buttermilk crispy
chicken house lean assess oh wow I don't
know what all these buttons do I haven't
tried them all yet I think it wobbles
yeah alright for anyone just tuning in
Ronnie 1997 with a 1997 volt latest ,
the latest this is the latest
colourfully car we did buy it
wow it has dumped us and E we're in it
even has power windows I'll buy it if
you take it to me where are usable bugsy
where are you Australia hey look at the
butt just looks kind of like a boat
though it also Pappa wheelie
it comes with a perfectly fit mattress
for the back well no we have to ask
Harold about that oh but it is a station
wagon RV guys were San Francisco it's
got tons of room for activities yeah you
could do a lot of activities on this guy
yeah yeah it depends on what you like to
do that's right
alright George we have 50 people left 50
people watching this shit yeah McDonald
sometime I feel a little bad for this go
piece that library they can turn in for
this they love it they're loving it
right now yeah double denim seatbelt
this car has airbags enjoying the move
no power tools you guys are great ok we
seriously need are like a thing to make
this car steer X Matic if you're out
there if you're ever gonna build
anything
whose ex medic they're people who are
never gonna ship anything Oh like a lot
of people in self-driving cars old cars
we got you old cars we got you wait ok
guys you didn't tell us this I'd watch
trying to turn the radio let's see the
answer I think maybe we should show all
right I'll show the outside you Scopus
what up this is Alex to make oh hell
yeah
wait to the light does have automatic
lights not as automatic lights fun
mm-hmm all right guys we'll show you the
exterior I'm a little concerned about
locking it then it won't on look well I
don't know how did the locks work oh
just just push your lock oh yeah check
it out now you know what wait if someone
steals it they might be doing us a favor
all right guys so this is the Volvo this
lovely car look at this it has wipers
for the headlight we took it at Burning
Man
Wow multiple times
how are the tire treads looking look at
how much tread is in these tires yeah
yeah this is all-terrain tire yeah
no these are Volvo we could sell for the
tires alone no we're not making it
self-driving we are looking to sell it
Oh check out that Wow look at that trunk
space this could be you this could be
you at Burning Man this year at Burning
Man this year in this Volvo yeah yeah
for only two thousand two thousand two
thousand dollars yeah
[Laughter]
oh that's nice oh that is so nice
no but guys seriously you know what you
really want to buy if you got like two
thousand dollars lying around you know
what you can get for half that a
midnight black e on a gray panda and a
giraffe of your choosing
today or we can finally do the Logan
Paul comment on the I slash o sharp how
about I actually redirects there it's
all part of our dude you should you
should do it wow this is good tag team
marketing shipping tomorrow we actually
if you buy it tonight we will
legitimately ship whatever you buy
unless it's a boss draft tomorrow I will
ship it myself I love to like we used to
stamp table they were terrible
yeah that's fulfilled by Shopify I was
great no like fries like in the
McDonald's dude I thought you were
eating healthy no fries let's get fries
yeah your friend sorry okay all right
bye bye bye score peace